export default data = [
  {
      question: "When John proposes an idea, people in his office always lend their support. He feels lucky to have ______ like them.",
      options: ["villains","executives","colleagues","intruders"],
      correct_option: "colleagues"
  },
  {
      question: "As last year’s MVP (Most Valuable Player), Joan is ______ to the basketball team. No other player can replace her.",
      options: ["indispensable","comprehensible","affordable","permissible"],
      correct_option: "indispensable"
  },
  {
      question: "The researcher warned that the results of the study needed to be interpreted with ______ because the sample size was not big enough to make firm conclusions.",
      options: ["metaphor","caution","enthusiasm","impulse"],
      correct_option: "caution"
  },
  {
      question: "Although the small group of soldiers was greatly ______ by their enemy, they fought with great courage and finally won the battle.",
      options: ["initiated","contradicted","outnumbered","triggered"],
      correct_option: "outnumbered"
  },
  {
      question: "Mr. Wise received an award for his ______ to the needy children and the elderly in the neighborhood.",
      options: ["competence","prospect","momentum","devotion"],
      correct_option: "devotion"
  },
  {
      question: "One simple yet good way to ______ your love for your family is to express it directly in words.",
      options: ["manifest","resemble","execute","instruct"],
      correct_option: "manifest"
  },
  {
      question: "Cloning animals has been very controversial. Some people consider it a medical breakthrough, while others think it is ______ and should be prohibited.",
      options: ["legitimate","inclusive","unethical","nonmilitant"],
      correct_option: "unethical"
  },
  {
      question: "Animals that stay in groups are more likely to find food and detect danger than a ______ animal—multiple pairs of eyes are better than one.",
      options: ["contagious","rigid","distinctive","solitary"],
      correct_option: "solitary"
  },
  {
      question: "On the first page of her new book, the writer ______ all the people who helped in the publication of the book.",
      options: ["contemplates","acknowledges","inquires","regulates"],
      correct_option: "acknowledges"
  },
  {
      question: "Due to the recession, it is not easy for people to get ______ paid jobs, even if they are highly educated and well-trained in the field.",
      options: ["compatibly","decently","relevantly","virtually"],
      correct_option: "decently"
  },
]